Yaroslav Catin

Expert Backend / Desktop developer (c#/c++/sql/js)

I have 19 years of experience in software development. I'm specialized in backend and desktop development using .NET / .NET Core (MVC, Web API), c#, c++, javascript, VSTO, etc. I participated in many successful projects from various industries such as security, CAD systems, 3d printing, and E-Commerce. I specialize in solving complex technical problems. For instance, if your project is complicated and required research, design, analysis skills, improving performance, deep knowledge in c#, c++, web, native code, algorithms, etc. Or when work has to be done on time with the best quality. Please look at feedback from my clients in "Back-End Development" and "Desktop Software Development" profiles. Their words will tell even more than my self-introduction.



lancerok8@gmail.com

Gandia, Spain

+1 337 335 0421

live:.cid.fb2c77cadcb439a4

4 8

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead developer / team lead famous cyber security company

04/2018 - Present

Senior Software Engineer Materialise

04/2014 - 05/2015

Achievements/Tasks

 Autocad development. Design and development of new CAD kernel (NeoGeoniCS) ObjectARX technology, Autocad .Net API

vehicle speed detection

Freelancer.com

01/2007 - 08/2007

Achievements/Tasks

Developed system for vehicle speed detection

EDUCATION

Computer science

National Technical University of Ukraine

1998 - 2003

SKILLS

C++ C# Python Reverse Engineering

Cracking Desktop

Desktop Application

Software Debugging

OpenCV

C

PHP

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Project Name

ACHIEVEMENTS

Achievement Name

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Spanish

Elementary Proficiency

INTERESTS

Coding